Extend y
za te wo nobashite Extend your hand, no need to fear
Cut thro ed to fear
ite Cut through the wind, and persevere
Chart your own cours evere
wn course, the time to push forward is here
Ina ti
gucha ni Video Editing Graphics fedew Datenshi In a time like a storm, hear the tidal waves roar.
youna jidai Soundtracking Timing Halee Gab we keep trudging along but we're still wanting more
Kizuki But in spite of it al more
rou to shita Quality Control Gab Pepperjack Galaxy 9000 Westfal Zenef Gol D. Rocks for ourselves was about to fall
i no ka douka nante Subtitle Editing Gol D. Rocks Gordingus Pollychan Zenef Who to ask? As if there's anyone listening
da Typesetting Gab Pollychan you'll never be one hundred percent sure
konde Translation Crunchyroll ghostDunk PamkinPingui But if you shut your eyes to the chaos,
and
ba and you'd only take a breath
Ukab When you ope
garu no wa a When you open up your eyes
ru no wa
i no shimesu michi you will find where you were meant to be
Exten
shite Extend your hand, no need to fear
Cut thro need to fear
te Sugh the wind, and persevere
Kura Kick out the
Kick out the dark until the sky clears
boku no tame ni Even as we act in our own best interests,
Ki doing wn best interests,
darou doing what we each believe is for our own
Chart your
chizu wo egaite yuke Chart your own course, the time to push forward is here
NEPACE
Banquet Ha Third Floor Inside the Castle Now then, I've got some samurai to snuff out.
But before that, I ought to finish the job at hand.
Caiman Lady. are you ready to broadcast his voice all over the island?
Yes. I am!
Black Leg...
Would you kindly summon Nico Robin at once?
REL
We're all ready to go...
helFlowe
< to 3 The Honorable Hyogoro the eFlower
Once you've touched my sticky. hard gum, you'll never escape.
I've coated the floor as well.
One wrong step and you're trapped.
On top of that, my girls are standing guard with tranquilizer guns in the back.
All that's left for you to do..
is call out for her!
Call Nico Robin!
Dz
Come on, call for help!
k*** have another matter to attend to!
X/
Robin...
I want... to join your crew.
- Huh?! -Huh?!
I want to live!
You sure are stubborn...
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Oh. I can't watch...
I'm going to cry...
That man won't let his friend come to harm!
He'd rather die than utter a single word!
If he wasn't our enemy. I might have fallen in love!
W-Wait!
Give me a minute...
to say a few words.
I bet he just wants to say something like "eat shit" before he dies!
Please don't!
Don't make her any angrier. or else...
Robin...
l... l...
l..
wanted to see your smile... one more time..
Help me, Robin!
- What?! What?!
He called her for help after all! - What?! -What?!
I'm on the third floor!
In the banquet hall!
I've been taken hostage!
I'm sorry!
Sanji...
They're gonna kill me if you don't come, Robin!
Help!
What the hell is that? Tallk about pathetic!
Is that one of the Straw Hats?!
/ /Listen to that! His voice is echoing across the entire island! WIVIWN
Nico Robin is one of the most important figures in the world.
They must be after her knowledge!
FR-U
V Sounds to me like an obvious trap for Robin!
Those are some pretty pathetic sounds coming from a man!
0 9
These guys are a riot!
I'd bet anything it's a woman.
111 What a pain...
Hey. Nami! -His voice is coming from up there!
Be careful!
You're my only hope! What's with that eye?
Come quickly!
Robin!
What a surprise.
I called for Robin.
Now, untie me.
What?!
Madame. someone's coming!
Already, huh?
You're not going anywhere.
Huh?!
Didn't you say you loved me?
//// Well, that means this isn't business anymore.
Now it's personal.
See those boys?
You'll be one of my precious pets, just like them.
You won't be able to live without my touch once I'm through with you.
- My heart belongs to Madame Black Maria alone... - My heart belongs to Madame Black Maria alone...
My heart...
belongs to all the ladies!
7 I forbid you to be unfaithful to me!
You need to be disciplined!
Hold on!
I wouldn't want to hurt a lady. so my armament haki is going soft!
Mil Fleurs!
Gigantesco Mano!
Spank!
**** **
* *
Madame Black Maria!
* ** ** * * * * * * R K * * * * * * * * *** * * * * * * # 1# *
How did you get in here?!
* *
I can bloom anywhere.
How dare you strike my face...
You really thought Id be so naive as to walk straight into your trap?
Robin!
**
I spent a lot of time in nefarious organizations.
When someone torments my friends..
I can't contain...
the devil within me!
Ah, pardon me!
I've cut you free with the icy chill of the underworld.
Brook!
Miss! They took down the tranquilizer unit!
All your spider silk traps..
...have been frozen and shattered, too!
It seems as though spider silk and the chil of the underworld go well together!
Monsters!
Look who's talking! Look who's talking!
Thank you!
You saved me...
* Think nothing of it.
T** ** *
T** Sorry about this, but I'm gonna go lend a hand to Kin'emon's group!
For some reason. I just can't see myself winning this one!
- You don't say.  You don't say.
Get back/here, Black Leg!
You're going to be my pet!
won't let you go!
Is that all?
* * * * * * *
**
Any more last words?
*****
* *
* K *** * * *
* * * * Yould die to save a man who'd sell out his own friends? *
No. Black Maria...
It seems you fail to understand...
just how wonderful friends can be.
AAN
Sanji!
**
** 11//1
Thank you for relying on me!
It makes me happy!
Ah, watch out.
The floor is frozen.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Thank you!
Forbidden Store Inside the Don
Why would there be smoke coming out of a mouse?
It's one of the Marys, the surveillance unit of my father's army.
It's a cyborg.
In other words, an animal/with mechanical body parts.
What?!
They wander around the island aimlessly.
but they share what they see with the human Marys!
What?! What?!
So. even in here...
11,
Hey, are you sure it's this storehouse?
This place is cursed. No one goes in there anymore.
It doesn't look like anyone went inside.
But they said this was the place!
There's no doubt about it!
Young Master Yamato
I mean, the next shogun is in there!
It sounds like there are many of them.
This place isn't safe anymore!
We must flee, Yamato!
Please show us a path that keeps Lord Momonosuke out of sight!
Shogun! Come on out!
Or else we'll bash the door in!
- One, two! One, two!
- One,two! - One, two!
They're breaking through!
Sorry. Momonosuke!
Whaaat?!
Hide in my clothes!
1/1
//1/
Let's go. Shinobu!
I told you to keep him out of their sight!
I know!
They'll see him if we don't take them all down!
That is not what I meant!
Damn you! Damn you!
W-We Gifters have this route blocked already!
You really shouldn't be fighting yet!
Silence!
Out of my way!
Bao Huang!
Are the Red Scabbards samurai still in the treasury?
Yes, they are!
Black Maria! Where are you now?!
I'm still in the banquet hall.
Alright! I'll go and finish off those samurai!
Even on the brink of death, there's no way in hell the Soaring Six can kill them!
Got it?! Stay out of this!
Jack...
You're underestimating me...
Although...
this works out in my favor.
Sweet Entanglement
I appreciate him taking care of that for me.
What in the world... is that?
Listen, Nico Robin...
Youll belong to Viceroy  Kaido soon...
It's inevitable.
No, thanks.
I'd rather die!
So cool!
Onigashima Entrance
You gave it your best. full-moon warriors!
Too bad the weather's not on your side!
//1 1//1
1/.11
Pedro...
ww
Listen!
You-gara must press on!
No matter what... I have to avenge Pedro...!
, — W
Avenge Pedro?!
That worthless fool deserved to die!
What was your plan after waltzing into the Big Mom Pirates' territory? Have a picnic?!
If you don't want your friends to die. why don't you go back to grazing in the forest?!
////
You can lick your wounds there!
Now then...
This alliance with the Beast Pirates doesn't bring me a lick of excitement...
but it's Mama's decision. so I guess it can't be helped...
We need to teach these kids that the Four Emperors are way out of their league!
Theytre running!
The enemy leader Momonosuke.
19 is moving away from...
the Forbidden Storeroom!
I cannot see Momonosuke at the moment!
But there can be no doubt!
Momonosuke is with Young Master Yamato and the kunoichi!
Momonosuke General ot Wano's Sar
It may be cramped and hard to breathe, but for whatever reason...
I feel as though I am in heaven!
Shinobu, this way!
111 They just keep coming!
We need to find a less visible route!
Don't worry!
They can't see us if we take them all out!
Like I told you, that is not what I meant!
11-1
I repeat!
3 Third Floor Inside the Castle Momonosuke, who escaped from the Forbidden Storehouse,
is with Young Master Yamato and the kunoichi!
For certain!
Another broadcast.
They're going after Momo and Shinobu!
Young Master Yamato?
Well, whatever...
Hey. which way is the Forbidden Storehouse?!
L-Like I'm gonna tell you.
Huh?!
I-It's near the entrance of the Skull Dome...
Back of the Castle Tower Dome Entrance Kin'emon's group is at the back of the castle tower... ..
Back of the Castle Tower Dome Entrance That's in the opposite direction of the Dome's entrance.
Kin'emon and the others are hurting bad...
Momo and Shinobu are being chased by the damn Gifters..
Which of them needs me more?!
This way?! That way?!
No time to think!
The ones who need me the most are...
definitely this way!
I can't...
This blue flame draws out my stamina, but...
I think that I am...
almost at my limit..
Fight it! Or youll turn into an ice ogre again!
You'll lose control, use up the rest of your energy. and die for sure this time!
Don't give up, young man!
Get a hold of yourself!
That tanuki is suffering the same pain as you, but he's still working hard on the antidote!
How could we give up before him?
B-Big Boss...
You look different...
Leave it to this old man!
It's time to show them...
samurai's resilience! a
Apoo, we can't fight anymore!
The antibody is right behind them, but we just can't break through their ironclad defense!
Why would His Awesomeness infect us too?! We're on his side!
He's not gonna save you no matter how much you bitch and moan!
Just kill that tanuki and get the antibody already!
Dammit!
Drake! That traitor!
Stop acting like a hero!
Drake isn't the only problem!
That withered old man recovered somehow!
The legendary boss of Wano's underworld!
Drake Former Soaring Six Member Hyogoro "the Flower' Saur-Saur Fruit: Allosaurus Legendary Boss of the Underworld 33 Hyogoro the Flower!
With those two monsters standing guard...
we have no chance of getting to that tanuki!
Why does he look like that?!
He was just a little old man a second ago!
He's changed back into the tower of a man that Kaido was dead set on recruiting!
Shaking with excitement. huh?
Big Boss!
Are you okay?!
Yeah...
I can feel a chill... however...
I still have faith in my spirit!
1 suppose catching this virus...
drew out the last of my strength leaving me within an inch of death.
So it's all come down to this..
With my remaining power...
even if it costs me my life...
* * I will cut down every last one..
of their major players!
Hey! Underbosses!
- Yes. Big Boss! - Yes, Big Boss!
I may not have much time left...
If that tanuki can't finish the cure and I turn into an ice ogre...
Do one thing for me first!
Don't hesitate...
to strike me down!
If you don't...
I'll cut you all down...
every last person friend or foe
until no one is left!
How can we...
But... if the big boss becomes an ice ogre...
nobody has a chance of stopping him...
I'm counting on you...
Alright then...
As a former member of the Mimawari-gumi I'd like to see what he's got...
You're some kind of legend, huh?
All I see is a washed-up swordsman!
You old fart!
Prepare yourself!
One-Sword Style of the Flower!
Flaming Hair...
of Holy Rage!
HOLY FLAMING RAGE HAIR OF
MB
MA
Just throw bodies at him! Go!
Hey, Oden...
I sometimes wish...
**
that we had challenged Kaido back in the days...
when we were at our peaks.
But now...
Kin'emon and the others...
have pulled off the perfect raid!
Furthermore...
I have gained a most interesting disciple!
Sir Straw Hat!
You have great potential.
You will continue to grow stronger and stronger!
1111 Remember this. 111
In a momenf of crisis...
your true power will'be revealed!
/////1 Lef us take down Kaido together!
You got it!
Using that ryuo you taught me...
I'll kick Kaido's ass!
There was neither a hint of deception nor conceit in those words.
I'm certain he'll master ryuo, grow even stronger...
grow stronger. even
and finally take down Kaido!
Keep watching, Oden!
I know in my heart that the land of Wano...
will see the dawn once again!
Whoa there!
The whole floor is gonna get wiped out!
Time to meet your maker. you old fool!
Phoenix Brand!
You better keep your eyes on me. Queen!
Marco!
That hurt!
Was that a shockwave or something. you punk?!
I'm the one you're fighting right now!
You can focus on attacking those samurai...
after you chop off my head!
Dammit! This guy just won't die!
//
Go to hell already!
SAR
Bluebird!
Time to finish you off!
You son of a bitch!
Don't push your luck!
Crane Talons!
Guess it's no surprise... Holding off couple guys worth over a billion ain't easy... a
111 111.
111 8 8
You bastard!
Come on already. tanuki..!
What's this? Is that Marco I spy over there?
Seems like he's taken a real...
licking.
Everyone's turning back into ice ogres!
Th-The fire's gone...
Help me!
Do it! This is what I want!
11,
It's as if the heavens themselves have granted me one final reward...
I was rotting away in a cell, just waiting to die.
and yet I made it all the way here...
However. if I continue to live. all of your lives are at risk!
Forgive me for putting you in this position...
but you must do this for me!
The rest of you will have to carry on in my stead...
The man known as Hyogoro the Flower.
leaves this world...
with no regrets!
TO BE CONTINDED